Hello everyone,
today we are talking about the most important financial plan in the world.
We have done many videos on this
channel. Term Plan. The
Plus version of iProtect Smart, which is the best plan in the term plan, is the
plan that has come up with many new features.
That is what we are talking about in today's video.
Watch the video till the end to know the details. When we
talk about term plan, we
always have to think about the
three
biggest risks in a human's life.
For a person, they are called three Ds: Death, Disease, Disability, which means
death can come at any time unknown or unexpected. Disease can come.
Accidental Load Disability can come. Once these
three are protected,
our insurance journey, personal
insurance journey, becomes somewhat safe. The
most important thing in it is
death, which means that no matter what happens to us at this second,
our family is protected.
Term Plan is a plan that protects us and our family.  If we
ask you about my case, if
I die, there are two risks that
my family will face. One is
emotional loss. No
one
can ever compensate for the emotional loss of a person. But the other loss is
financial loss. A plan that allows me to give the
amount I make every month to my family. In
the world, that is, in India, look now. Out of
25 insurance companies, only health and life
insurance companies have term plans
.  No other product can
replace it.  Therefore, a
term plan is a must-have plan in your portfolio.
Today we are talking about one of the best plans out there.
Watch the video till the end to know all the details about the iProtect Smart Plus plan.   There are
many variations, meaning
we can opt for an event that increases in size depending on the life stage
.  A facility that
increases the sum of money by taking a lifestyle marriage, having children, etc. Similarly, if
we have a financial problem,
we can take a premium break for a year, and so on.
Many
new things have been added, that is,
iProtect Smart was the previous plan, and
iProtect Smart Plus is the plan that has added many things to it. Watch the
video till the end to know its details. If this is your
first time watching this channel, let me
introduce myself. My name is Binoy. I have
been working in the field of insurance, investment and banking for the last 20 years.
[Music]
Before I start talking about the term plan, I want to give you an idea of ​​its importance. I have been
working in this insurance field for 20 years.  The most important thing
I have learned in my 20 years working in this insurance field is
this one term insurance plan.  Because this is a
plan that everyone should take, but many
people are not aware of
it.  As for me,
I have seen deaths in my personal life,
meaning I have seen people die at a young age
.  So, at such a time, when
we have our family,
our
family that supports us, our wife and
children, the
most important plan is to ensure that no one suffers. I am in the
insurance field because I understand that
term insurance plan and health insurance
plan are the two things that
we make this field of insurance and the
reason why I am in insurance. I have
two
answers to the question of why I am in insurance. One is term insurance
plan and one is health insurance plan.
Therefore, we should
take the best plan. One of the best plans is the
plus version of iProtect Smart.
Its important points. First, let's see
what are the main
changes, that is, the normal term insurance
plan had iProtect Smart, which has
come as a plus version. Let's see what are the add-
ons that have come. One is
critical illness cover. It covers 60
critical illnesses. In this, 34 illnesses were covered. In the
previous Hyper
Smart, 30 illnesses were covered.
60 Illnesses are covered, which means that as soon as
any illness occurs, the
amount of critical illness will be paid immediately.
60 Illnesses are covered.
Similarly, there is a feature that will pay lacs on death intimation. That is, if
we give a death intimation to someone who has a sum of more than one crore rupees,
after giving the intimation, its death certificate and its paperwork, we
can release 3 lacs to the beneficiary's account the next day. That is, we will immediately set aside
a sum for this and
then
process the deep claim and then
pay the remaining amount.   It
's a great feature that will be delivered the next day.  Because
giving a quick help of Rs. 3 lakh
is a feature that no other company has.  It's the best feature.   There is
also a feature called the premium brake option
.  That is, if there is a financial
crisis, there is an
option to take a premium break for a year.
I will
explain all this in detail in the video. Similarly, regular
pay is what most
people choose,
meaning that it is paid continuously and regularly.
However, a new system
has been introduced for some time.
Limited Pay is a system that can be paid off in a short period of time, in five
years, in seven years.
Limited Pay has
come. As everyone knows, a
customer who took regular pay does not
have the option to switch to limited pay in the current situation.
But in this plan, we have the option to take a plan now and
make it a limited payment in the future.  That's a feature
.  Similarly, the
amount will increase depending on the life stage. The option to increase the amount is available when there is a major life stage change such as marriage,
having children, having a first
child, a second child, or
taking out a home loan
.
Similarly, discounts are available for salaried persons
.  These are the features of this plan.
I will tell you in detail what are the features of this plan. This is just that.
What are the important USPS of this plan?
First, it was said that
critical illness will
cover 60 critical illnesses. This is an optional rider.
We have to choose it as an optional rider
because usually we take a
term plan of one crore or one and a half crores and we have to take it
as an optional rider. We can take
60 illnesses
or take 20 illnesses. Once
any one of these illnesses is found out,
how much will it be given? This
means that we can take critical illness from one lakh to one and a half crores. That is, if we take the plan and take one
crore, we can take a
critical illness of one crore.
That means, after critical cases come,
one crore will be released.
After that, if death occurs in the future, the
other death will
get one crore, that is, but only if it is equal to the sum assured.
Criticals are only available, that is, up
to Rs. 1.5 crore. If there is a
problem of Rs. 1.5 crore, then you can
take a critical problem of Rs. 1.5 crore. But if
a person takes a plan of Rs. 1 crore, the
maximum limit of criticals is Rs.
1 crore. That is all. Equal to sumshot, that is, only the sumshot equal to the life sum can be taken for critical illness. Similarly, accidental death coverage is also available in this, that is, you can take an accidental death sumshot up to Rs. 3 crore.
This is also like this. If you
take a life cover of Rs.
1 crore, you can take an accident cover of Rs. 1 crore. This
means that if an accidental death
occurs, we will also get that one crore
plus the incident of accidental death. There
are two features
in this, namely, accidental death was in the old plan,
but the critical was
increased to 60 diseases. This is a change brought in this Critical I Protect
Sparta Plus. The
next is instant pay out
on  Intimation of Death Claim is a
new feature that
no company has yet. After filing a death claim and
submitting the death certificate and its papers, Rs
3 lakh will be released to the nominee's account the next day. However, there is
one condition in it:
this facility is available only to customers who have chosen a sum of Rs 1 crore or more
.  It is only available if death occurs three years after taking out the policy
.  These two things
come into play.  But it is a good feature because it may
take a few days, 10, 20 or 30 days, to
process our death claim,
but we
get an amount the next day itself, which is a big
sudden shock.
A feature that releases 3 lakhs to support the nominee
is available in this plan.
I think that's the best feature
.  If you like the video,
please press the like button.
The video reaches others based on your likes
.  So
press the like button anyway.  This is
a question everyone asks when taking out a plan.  If a financial crisis comes,
I'll make a plan now.
A short answer to how to pay premiums if a financial crisis occurs.
I wouldn't say it's a great answer.  The
premium break option has been
introduced in this plan as a small solution, meaning that
we can take a one-year break,
meaning that we are
paying the premium and a
big crisis comes up, then we can take a one-year
premium break. If there is a problem or death during that premium
break, we will get the same amount next year when we pay the
premium. There
are a few conditions in this. The
company must be informed 30 days in advance. That is, the
company must be informed 30 days before taking the premium break. Then the
first five years, that is, the policy of the policy will
sometimes be a policy that lasts 20 or 30 years
.  This is
only available in the regular pay policy.  This is not available for
the first five
years and the last three years of a policy that runs for the first 30 years.
That is, I
gave the example of 30 years, but the first five years
of the policy and the last three
years of the policy are not available.
After five years, you
can take a premium break once every five years, from then until the 10th.
Then, from 11 to 15, it
means taking a premium break.  In
case of crisis of funds, you
can take a feature like this.  Never been
before.  That's just
an added feature.
Then there's a new feature called Limited Pay, which has been around for a while,
four or five years
.  That means the plan now will be a 30 or 40
year plan.  But there's no
need to pay for 40 years.  It can be
paid off in five years.  There is a feature
called Limited Pay because people like NRIs cannot make a long-term commitment
.  But what is included in this plan? If a
customer who has taken regular pay now takes a 40-year plan and
pays for all 40 years and
says that he can pay the premium every year, sometimes after three or five
years, if the lifestyle salary is
high or the person's finances
improve, he can convert it to Limited Pay and pay the
premium quickly. This is
a feature available in this plan.
This is an additional feature.
Discounts are available for salaried individuals. This plan offers 10 to
15 percent discount.
For more details, if you
WhatsApp me, I will tell you
how the discounts come.
Similarly, the boundary conditions
are mandatory medicals, i.e. the
minimum to take this plan is 50 lakhs. The problem is that
mandatory medicals, i.e. physical,
we go to the lab and medical is mandatory for
any individual, i.e. even if it is 50
lakhs.  There is
no medical waiver from the beginning, you have to have medical, the
minimum is Rs 1 lakh, the maximum is the low limit, the
maximum
limit is determined based on our financial underrating and medical underrating, the limited pay
means I said pay for a while and then in the long term
we
get some shot, limited pay for 10-15 years,
we have the limited pay
option and then up to 60, which is chosen by
many people in India, pay the premium
till the age of 60,
my policy is till the age of 85, I
get one crore if I die, I can pay the premium till the age of 60,
I have
done it in such a way that in the hope that we will have an income gap till the age of 60, after that,
then
generally that is how it is for Indians,
retirement is 58-60, up to the age of 60,
that is, more people in India
opt to
pay the premium at the age of 60  More and more people are choosing the scheme with coverage up to the age of 70, 75, or 80.
Regular pay is also
available in this. Age entry: Those between the ages of 18 and
60 can
join this plan. Mode of payment: Annual, Half
Yearly, and Monthly. Minimum
education qualification
is HS, Higher Secondary, but there
are some conditions. If it is higher secondary with
salary, then this much income is required. If it is higher secondary with salary, then this much income is required for a person
doing business with higher secondary. If it is salaried, then if it is a
degree graduate, then this much salary is required. If it is
higher secondary with this much salary, then this much salary is required. If you want
to know about it, then
I will tell you the details after you WhatsApp me.  I Protect
Smart ICI
Prudential's best term insurance
plan is its plus version IPS Plus
version. I like the video. To like it, you have to like it. To
purchase this plan or
compare and purchase other term plans, you
can WhatsApp me or
call me. If you have not subscribed to this channel yet,
subscribe.
This
channel makes informative videos like this. If you click on the bell icon,
you will get a
notification when we upload a video. Also click on the bell icon.
So,
until the next video, bye bye to everyone.